# Natalia Kirieieva

JUNIOR FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- nataliakireewa@gmail.com
- +38068-100-3771
- github
- in LinkedIn

# SKILLS

#### FRONT-END:

- JavaScript
- React/Redux
- React Native
- Bootstrap
- MUI
- TypeScript

#### **BACK-END:**

- Node.is
- Express.js
- Amazon EC2
- MongoDB
- SQL
- Python
- C

#### **GENERAL:**

- Agile methodology
- Remote work
- Test Driven Development Authentication
- Git

# **EDUCATION**

- Certificate in CS50's
   Introduction to Computer
   Science | Harvard Online
   Course (2023)
- Certificate in Full Stack
   Web Development |
   Parsity Software
   Engineering School (2023)
- Master's degree of international economics and management | Kyiv National Economics University (2009)

# LANGUAGES

- Ukrainian, Russian (Fluent)
- English (Upper-Intermediate)
- Spanish (Intermediate)

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Former video producer with 10+ years experience in video production, planning, budgeting and media. Completed full-stack Software Development program focused on Javascript, React, Node, Python, MongoDB. Excited to be considered for full-stack roles to contribute to an organization and learn more about the industry directly.

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Software Engineering Student** | Parsity

6/2022 - 1/2023



• An app designed to provide recommendations for a baby's sleep schedule and display nearby playgrounds on an interactive map.

## **Technologies Used:**

- Frontend: React/Redux, Yup, React Google Maps API.
- Backend: MongoDB/Mongoose, Node, Express, Google Maps API Web Services, Passport, Twilio SendGrid Mail Send API.
- Deployment: Heroku.

# <u>CallWaiter</u>Bot

 Elevate beach bar service with CallWaiterBot – a one-touch solution for customers, seamlessly integrated with Telegram for staff coordination.

#### **Technologies Used:**

- Frontend: React, React Context, Material-UI (MUI), and internationalization (i18n).
- Backend: server built with Python & Gunicorn on Amazon EC2.
- · Deployment: Netlify.

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

## Video Producer | Freelance Contractor

7/2017-8/2020

 Planned, budgeted, communicated, and handled emergencies within pre-production, post production, and production processes.

#### **Digital Producer** | Prodigy Agency

7/2018-12/2018

5/2015-11/2019

- Assisted with the creation of new designs, preparation of reports, and estimating costs.
- Supervised the creation of web advertisements, videos, and other media.

## Venue & Broadcast Producer | Sports Production

- Contributed to 4 projects, including 2nd European Games in Baku, World Weightlifting Championship in Ashgabat, 4th Islamic Solidarity Games in Baku, Judo Grand Slam in Baku.
- Managed all aspects of sports presentation, including pre-production, logistics planning, timeline creation, and scheduling teams.